Guide to the Frances Hesselbein Papers, 1942-2013 AIS.2013.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Frances Hesselbein Institute Papers, 1942-2014; A.
  - Audio/Visual material, 1985-2013, undated; VIII.
    - The Leader to Leader Institute, 2003-2011; 2.
      - Innovators: Lessons from the Social Sector - Regina Herzlinger interview part 1, December 7, 2005 (Box 40, Video 3)
      - Innovators: Lessons from the Social Sector - Regina Herzlinger interview part 2, December 7, 2005 (Box 40, Video 4)
      - Innovators: Lessons from the Social Sector - Jim Collins interview pt. 1, December 16, 2005 (Box 40, Video 5)
      - Innovators: Lessons from the Social Sector - Jim Collins interview pt. 2, December 16, 2005 (Box 40, Video 6)
      - Innovators: Lessons from the Social Sector - Bill Pollard interview, November 29, 2005 (Box 40, Video 7)
      - Innovators: Lessons from the Social Sector, 2006 (Box 40, Disk 1)
      - The 5 Most Important Questions/Self-Assessment Tool, 2000s (Box 40, Disk 2)
      - BoardEffect Admin training, February 12, 2009 (Box 40, Disk 3)
      - Leader to Leader printed materials files, undated (Box 40, Disk 4-5)
      - Focus: HOPE - University of Michigan conference photos, December 2003 (Box 40, Disk 6)
      - The Five Most Important Questions summary, June 2008 (Box 40, Disk 7)
      - Leader to Leader Holiday Party photos, December 14, 2004 (Box 40, Disk 8)
      - Leader to Leader 15th Anniversary dinner photos, April 20, 2005 (Box 40, Disk 9)
      - Leader to Leader Holiday Party photos, December 15, 2005 (Box 40, Disk 10)
      - Leader to Leader's Leader of the Future Award dinner photos, 2006 (Box 40, Disk 11)
      - Leader to Leader Holiday Party photos, December 14, 2006 (Box 40, Disk 12)
      - Leader to Leader's Leader of the Future Award dinner photos, November 19, 2007 (Box 40, Disk 13)
      - Leader to Leader Holiday Party photos, December 18, 2008 (Box 40, Disk 14)
      - Leader to Leader's Leader of the Future Award dinner, November 2, 2009 (Box 40, Disk 15)
      - Leader to Leader Holiday Party photos, December 17, 2009 (Box 40, Disk 16)
      - Leader to Leader's Leader of the Future Award dinner, October 11, 2010 (Box 40, Disk 17)
      - Leader to Leader Holiday Party photos, 2010 (Box 40, Disk 18)
      - Leader to Leader Holiday Party photos, December 16, 2010 (Box 40, Disk 19)
      - Leader to Leader's Leader of the Future Award dinner photos, November 1, 2011 (Box 40, Disk 20)
      - Leader to Leader Holiday Party photos, December 15, 2011 (Box 40, Disk 21)
      - Alliance Annual Conference - Leader to Leader sessions photos, August 2004; 27. (Box 40, Disk 22)
      - Leader to Leader Holiday party contact sheets, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Frances Hesselbein Leadership Institute, 2012-2013; 3.
      - Hesselbein Leadership Institute Leader of the Future Award dinner photos, October 16, 2012 (Box 40, Disk 23)
      - Hesselbein Leadership Institute Holiday Party photos, December 13, 2012 (Box 40, Disk 24)
      - Hesselbein Leadership Institute dinner, October 21, 2013 (Box 40, Disk 25)
    - Peter F. Drucker, 1985-2009; 4.
      - Peter F. Drucker Speech to the Independent Sector, October 22, 1990 (Box 41, Video 1)
      - Meeting the Challenge w/ Warren Bennis - ft. Peter Drucker, undated (Box 41, Video 2)
      - Peter Drucker on Self-Assessment, undated (Box 41, Video 3)
      - Drucker conference speech via video recording, January 21, 1998 (Box 41, Video 4)
      - Dr. Peter Drucker on "Non-Profit Organizations", October 17, 2000 (Box 41, Video 5)
      - Peter Drucker on "The Discipline of Innovation", September 19, 1997 (Box 41, Video 6)
      - Tape 1 - Peter Drucker on "Cardinal Spellman", May 2, 1997 (Box 41, Video 7)
      - Tape 2 - Peter Drucker on "Alfred Sloan", May 2, 1997 (Box 41, Video 8)
      - Tape 3 - Peter Drucker on "Eric Dombrofski", May 2, 1997 (Box 41, Video 9)
      - Tape 4 - Peter Drucker on "Jim Webb", May 2, 1997 (Box 41, Video 10)
      - Tape 5 - Peter Drucker on "General Marshall", May 2, 1997 (Box 41, Video 11)
      - Tape 6 - Peter Drucker on "Frances Hesselbein", May 2, 1997 (Box 41, Video 12)
      - Tape 7 - Peter Drucker "Summation", May 2, 1997 (Box 41, Video 13)
      - "Peter Drucker - Innovacion", undated (Box 41, Video 14)
      - "Peter Drucker - Management", undated (Box 41, Video 15)
      - "Peter Drucker - Autoevaluacion", undated (Box 41, Video 16)
      - "Peter Drucker - Una Asociacion Vital", undated (Box 41, Video 17)
      - "Peter Drucker - Mision y Estrtegia", undated (Box 41, Video 18)
      - "Peter Drucker - Fund Raising", undated (Box 41, Video 19)
      - "Peter Drucker Tribute", undated (Box 41, Video 20)
      - Peter F. Drucker speech to the Independent Sector, October 22, 1990 (Box 41, Video 21)
      - Meeting the Collaboration Challenge with Warren Bennis and Peter Drucker, undated (Box 41, Video 22)
      - "A dialogue with Frances Hesselbein and Peter Drucker", September 1989 (Box 41, Video 23)
      - Jack Welch - Drucker Archives Opening, undated (Box 41, Video 24)
      - The Drucker Center - The Claremont Graduate School, undated (Box 41, Video 25)
      - Peter Drucker on the Kennedy Institute, undated (Box 41, Video 26)
      - Bob Buford interview with Peter Drucker, August 17, 1998 (Box 41, Video 27)
      - "Atlanta Video", June 15, 1995 (Box 41, Video 28)
      - Peter Drucker - The New Models: Church of the 21st Century, August 19, 1991 (Box 41, Cassette 1)
      - Peter Drucker - The New Models: Church of the 21st Century, August 20, 1991 (Box 41, Cassette 2)
      - The Changing World of the Executive: Mastering Managerial Pressure Points, 1985 (Box 41, Cassette 3)
      - Peter Drucker interview by Michele Hunt, undated (Box 41, Disk 1)
      - Peter F. Drucker presentation, undated (Box 41, Disk 2)
      - "The Discipline of Innovation" - Fall Conference presentation, 1997 (Box 41, Disk 3)
      - Peter Drucker Acceptance speech - Distinguished Community Service Award, 1991 (Box 41, Disk 4)
      - Business Matters - The Life and Times of Peter Drucker, 1991 (Box 41, Disk 5)
      - Peter Drucker: A Living Legacy, 1999 (Box 41, Disk 6)
      - Peter Drucker: An Intellectual Journey, undated (Box 41, Disk 7)
      - A Tribute to Peter F. Drucker, April 20, 2005 (Box 41, Disk 8)
      - The Drucker School video magazine, 2008-2009 (Box 41, Disk 9)
      - The Drucker Legacy Symposium - Speaker overview, May 2006 (Box 41, Disk 10)
      - The Drucker Legacy - Breakfast with Doris Drucker, May 12, 2006 (Box 41, Disk 11)
      - The Drucker Legacy - President's Dinner, Jim Collins presentation, May 12, 2006 (Box 41, Disk 12)
      - The Nonprofit Drucker Vol. 1, 1989 (Box 41, Disk 13-17)
      - The Nonprofit Drucker Vol. 2, 1989 (Box 42, Disk 1-5)
      - The Nonprofit Drucker Vol. 3, 1989 (Box 42, Disk 6-10)
      - The Nonprofit Drucker Vol. 4, 1989 (Box 42, Disk 11-15)
      - The Nonprofit Drucker Vol. 5, 1989 (Box 42, Disk 16-20)
- Frances Hesselbein Personal Papers, ca. 1930s-1940s, 1955-2014; B.
  The Frances Hesselbein Personal Papers are a subgroup of the overall Frances Hesselbein collection. The records contained in this group are of both a personal and professional nature, though they relate to Hesselbein's life outside of The Drucker Foundation and its later versions. This subgroup therefore includes information pertaining to Hesselbein's relationship with the Girl Scouts of the United States of America, both during her time in that organization and after. There is information on publications from Hesselbein herself, such as specific materials related to the creation of her autobiography. Press and event materials contained in the subgroup relate to both Hesselbein and her colleagues or organizations with which she was associated. Hesselbein's speeches dating back to the mid-1970s are also included here. The media for this subgroup includes materials from the Girl Scouts, but focuses mainly on Hesselbein herself, with some material from her family as well. The media materials are mainly dated from the 1980s to the present day, though there are some items that originate from the earlier times.
  - Girl Scouts of the United States of America, 1968-2013; I.
    This series contains documents from Frances Hesselbein's time as CEO of the Girl Scouts, as well as later years. It includes correspondence, management publications, board meeting materials, event plans and information, management reports, and items such as the organizational newsletter announcing Hesselbein as the new CEO. There are a variety of materials dealing with the 100th anniversary celebration that occurred in 2012, including conference information, correspondence, and a book from the Girl Scouts on the topic. The documents range from 1968-2012, and media for the Girl Scouts may be found in Series IX of this subgroup.
    - Administrative Material, 1973-1990; 1. (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - GSUSA Nat'l Board Position Information, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - GSUSA Nat'l Board Meeting Materials, January 1987- May 1987 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - GSUSA Nat'l Board Meeting Materials, September 1987- October 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - GSUSA Nat'l Board Meeting Materials, January 1988- August 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - GSUSA Nat'l Board Meeting Materials, November 1988- May 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - GSUSA Nat'l Board Meeting Materials, October 1989- January 1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - GSUSA Nat'l Board Executive Committee Materials, December 1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - GSUSA Nat'l Tactical Plan, Integrated Objectives #1-4, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - GSUSA Nat'l Tactical Plan, Integrated Objectives #5-11, E-1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - GSUSA Nat'l Staff listings, organizational diagrams, 1973-1988 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - GSUSA Nat'l Plans for delivery of service, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Board Meeting evaluations with prayer for Frances, January 1990 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Directory of Former National Directors, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Management Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Publications, 1968-2012; 2.
      - Colloquium on the Year 2000, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Girl Scout Leader, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - GSUSA Individual Councils' publications, 1999-2011 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - GSUSA National Summaries and Reports, 2007-2012 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Girl Scout Monographs and Nat'l Board information, 1987-2012 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Girl Scout Monographs, 1978-1999 (Box 15, Folder 22-25)
      - Girl Scout Newsletters, 1976-2012 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Kathy Cloninger - Tough Cookies, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - 100th Anniversary of the Girl Scouts, 2011-2012; 3.
      - Girl Scouts: A Celebration of 100 Trailblazing Years, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - GSUSA 100th Anniversary event correspondence, 2011-2012 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - GSUSA 100th Anniversary event materials, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - GSUSA 100th Anniversary Conferences, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Events, 2000-2011; 4.
      - Hesselbein Luncheon and Women's Forum, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - GSUSA Overseas North Atlantic Award recipients, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - GSUSA Conference materials, 2008-2011 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - Event photographs, 1970s-1980s, 2000s (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1989-2013; 5.
      - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 2008-2013 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Publications, 1960-2013; II.
    This series includes different forms of publications, including books, workbooks, journals, and some magazines, dated from 1960-2013. The books include those written by Frances Hesselbein, or those featuring her in some form. They are organized chronologically by publication date. Many of the records in this series deal with Hesselbein's process for writing, including materials sent to colleagues for editing, and correspondence on the matters of Hesselbein's books. These materials also include the drafts of excerpts from Hesselbein's books. There are also publications from organizations with which Hesselbein was affiliated or in whose activities she was interested, such as a newsletter from the Daughters of the American Revolution. The inclusion of these items provides a view of other organizations Hesselbein considers important or worthwhile.
    - Frances Hesselbein writings, 1960-2009; 1.
      - Articles by Frances Hesselbein, 1960-2009 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - "Ban the Hierarchy" notes for book, 1990s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Book chapter drafts, 2000s (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Book excerpts, 1990s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Book introductions - drafts, 2000s (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Book leadership notes, 1990s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - "Managing for the mission" book notes, 1990s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Book notes, 1990s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Book preface, 1990s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Book excerpt drafts, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Autobiographical excerpt drafts - "Darkness of Our Times", 2000s (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Autobiographical excerpt drafts and references, 2000s (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Autobiographical excerpts and references - Girl Scouts, 2000s (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Autobiographical excerpt draft - "If Wisdom's Ways You Would Wisely Seek", 2009 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Autobiographical excerpt drafts - "Leadership is a Journey", 1990s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Autobiographical excerpt drafts - "Learning Along the Way", 1990s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Autobiography draft - "My Journey: Serving is Living", 2000s (Box 16, Folder 21-22)
      - Autobiographical excerpt drafts - "September 11, 2001", 2000s (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Autobiographical excerpt drafts - "Shine a Light", 2000s (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Autobiographical excerpt drafts - "Two Awkward Questions", 2000s (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Autobiographical excerpt draft - "U.S. Army - Its Culture", 2000s (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Untitled autobiographical book excerpts, 1990s-2000s (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Book reference - Eisenhower Nat'l Security Conference speech, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Book reference - Harvard Business Review, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Book reference - "What It Means to Belong" speech, 1976, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Book reference - "Women at the Top", 1999-2008 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - My Life in Leadership writing plans, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - My Life in Leadership foreword draft, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - My Life in Leadership introduction draft, 2009-2011 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - My Life in Leadership references/notes - "Doors I Opened on My Journey", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 35-36)
      - My Life in Leadership references - How I Became Who I Am, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft/correspondence - "Adventures Around the World", 2010-2011 (Box 16, Folder 38)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "Called to Serve", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 39)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "Changed Hearts, Changed Minds", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 40)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "Choose Your Battles", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 41)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "Daisy Girl Scouts", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 42)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "Doors that Opened", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 43)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "GS Troop 17", 2009-2011 (Box 16, Folder 44)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "The Heart of the Organization", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 45)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "If Wisdom's Ways", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 46)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "Leaders of the Future", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 47)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "Mama Wicks/The Defining Moment", 2007-2011 (Box 16, Folder 48)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "The Military", 2009-2011 (Box 16, Folder 49)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "My Father, My Hero", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 50)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "My Name is Frances Ann", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 51)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft - "You Can Leave the Job, You Never Leave the Movement", 2009-2011 (Box 16, Folder 52)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt drafts and references - "Never the President", 2009-2011 (Box 16, Folder 53)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "New York Calls", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 54)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "Peter Drucker", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 55)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "The Philosophy of No Surprises", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 56)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "The Power of No", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 57)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "Shine A Light", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 58)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "Staying Cool", August 2009 (Box 16, Folder 59)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "Take Care of Your Sister", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 60)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "Time for Transformation", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 61)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "Journey to Transformation", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 62)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "Two Great Women", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 63)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "Two Unusual Conversations", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 64)
      - My Life in Leadership excerpt draft "When Does the Sled Take Off?", 2011 (Box 16, Folder 65)
      - Book correspondence notes/drafts - Alan Shrader, 2008-2010 (Box 16, Folder 66)
      - Book materials sent to Alan Shrader, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 67-68)
      - Book correspondence and notes - Elizabeth Edersheim, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 69)
      - Collaboration Challenge Reader Guide, undated (Box 16, Folder 70)
      - Leading Beyond the Walls guide, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 71)
      - Leading Beyond the Walls - Peter Drucker chapter, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 72)
      - Leading Beyond the Walls - William Bridges chapter, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 73)
      - Leading Beyond the Walls - Noel Tichy chapter, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 74)
      - Leading Beyond the Walls - Dave Ulrich chapter, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 75)
      - Leading Beyond the Walls - Patrick Waide chapter, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Outside publications, 1996-2003, 2013; 2.
      - Daughters of the American Revolution Newsletter, 2013 (Box 16, Folder 77)
      - Coaching Development, Careers and Performance workbook, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 78)
      - Joel Barker - Wealth, Innovation, and Diversity workbook, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 79)
      - Josephson Institute of Ethics Report Card on Integrity, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Books, 1993, 2004-2013; 3.
      - EuroCharity Yearbook: Leadership for Sustainability, 2011-2012 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Governing, Leading, and Managing Nonprofit Organizations, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Finishing Well, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - My Life in Leadership (Serbian translation), 2013 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Female Leadership: Die Macht der Frauen (German text), 2011 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1989-2014, undated; III.
    The correspondence in this series is both professional and personal, and does not include the correspondence between board members of the organization Frances Hesselbein has helped to lead. It includes thank you notes, handwritten letters between friends, correspondence dealing with proposed projects, and letters from Frances Hesselbein of a professional nature. The letters are in alphabetized folders, which are then organized chronologically. Some files contain information on things mentioned in the letters, which were included here in order to preserve context. The correspondence dates range from 1989-2014, though for some materials no date was discernable.
    - Alexander, Hannah, September 8, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Alvarez, Jeannette, February 6, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - American Institute of Certified Public Accountants, December 16, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - American Management Association, January 28, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - Army correspondence, 1999-2012 (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, August-September 1993 (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - Atlanta Executive Service Corps, June-September 1992 (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - Austin, Lloyd, 2009-2011 (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - Autobiography endorsements, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - Babson College, 2011-2012 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Bakke, Dennis, March 1, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Bayers, William G., September 6, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Beckhard, Richard, November 1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Bennis, Warren, 1991-1992, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Berenato, Agnus, 2008-2010 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
    - Berry, Richard, April-May 2012 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Birmingham-Southern College, August-September 1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Birthday wishes, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Blocker, Marilyn, June 2012 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Boardmember's Forum, December 1996 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Book introductions, 1997-2004 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Breakthrough Newsletter, June 12, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Bright China Group, 2011-2012 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Buford, Robert, 1989-2014 (Box 18, Folder 16-19)
    - Business Week article correspondence, March-April 1990 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Buttrick, Kathryn, June 1991 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Calvary Fund, Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Canadian Drucker Award, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Casey, George, 2009-2011 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies, February 24, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Center for Women and Philanthropy, August 1992 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Chowdhury, Subir, February 16, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Ciecka, Richard, January 4, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Class of 1951 Leadership Chair, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Cloninger, Kathy, January 23, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Community Anti-Drug Coalitions of America, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Connecticut Valley Girl Scouts Woman of Merit Award, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Council of Community Services, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Crutchfield, Leslie, November 1993 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Dellone, Vicki, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Dilenschneider, Robert, 2011-2013 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Dorf, Richard, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Dropkin, Murray, August 2001 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Evans School of Public Affairs - U. of Washington, 2011-2012 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Executive Development Associates, November 1992 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Executive Development Roundtable, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Family Service America Large Agency Executive's conference, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Fairfield University John M. Olin Lecture press correspondence, November 5, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Flores, Jesse, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Fundacion Compromiso, July 25, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Gardner, John, November 27, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Geneva Bolton Johnson Leadership Award Luncheon, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Ghana correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Girl Scouts of Eastern Massachusetts, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Girl Scouts of Eastern PA Centennial Award, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Girl Scouts of the Philippines, September 23, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Girl Scouts Overseas, March 5, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Girl Scouts - Wapehani Council, November 22, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 52)